Who would've thought
من كان ليظن
that Lin Mojiao is actually crazy?
هل لين موجياو مجنونة بالفعل؟
He managed to avoid the penalty this time.
لقد تمكن من تجنب ركلة الجزاء هذه المرة.
Do you think he did it on purpose?
هل تعتقد أنه فعل ذلك عن قصد؟
How could it be such a coincidence?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا محض صدفة؟
Then let him stay in the mental hospital
ثم دعه يبقى في مستشفى الأمراض العقلية
forever.
للأبد.
So, what's next?
إذن، ما الخطوة التالية؟
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
I'm going to get Xu Meng back.
سأستعيد شو مينغ.
Good luck.
حظ سعيد.
How's the orphanage charity foundation
كيف حال مؤسسة رعاية الأيتام الخيرية
on the orphanage foundation?
على مؤسسة دار الأيتام؟
Almost done.
أوشكت على الانتهاء.
When are you going to tell Ms. Xu?
متى ستخبر السيدة شو؟
Lu Xing,
لو شينغ,
do you know?
هل تعلم؟
I went for another prenatal check-up yesterday.
ذهبتُ أمس لإجراء فحص ما قبل الولادة آخر.
The doctor said
قال الطبيب
our baby is very healthy.
طفلنا يتمتع بصحة جيدة جداً.
So you have to wake up soon.
لذا عليك أن تستيقظ قريباً.
Let's go meet the baby together.
هيا بنا نلتقي بالطفل معًا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Wenjie,
وينجي،
It's not good for the baby
هذا ليس جيداً للطفل
to have such mood swings during pregnancy.
أن تعاني من تقلبات مزاجية حادة أثناء الحمل.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I must make sure he
يجب أن أتأكد من أنه
gets to see a healthy baby.
يحظى برؤية طفل سليم معافى.
I've talked to the doctor.
لقد تحدثت مع الطبيب.
His condition is improving.
حالته تتحسن.
So, the most important thing for you now
إذن، أهم شيء بالنسبة لك الآن
is to take good care of yourself.
هو أن تعتني بنفسك جيداً.
I will.
أنا سوف.
I still have to wait for him to wake up.
ما زلت أنتظر استيقاظه.
The shareholders are already
المساهمون بالفعل
waiting for you in the conference room.
أنتظرك في قاعة المؤتمرات.
Mr Lin II was sent abroad when he was young.
أُرسل السيد لين الثاني إلى الخارج عندما كان صغيراً.
Can he manage the company?
هل يستطيع إدارة الشركة؟
It's ridiculous
هذا أمر سخيف
to appoint a person
لتعيين شخص
who is not familiar with the company
الشخص الذي ليس على دراية بالشركة
as the chairman.
بصفته رئيسًا.
How about
ماذا عن
letting the board of directors nominate
السماح لمجلس الإدارة بالترشيح
and then re-election?
ثم إعادة انتخابه؟
What can a young man do?
ماذا يمكن لشاب أن يفعل؟
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي وسادتي،
the former chairman,
الرئيس السابق،
Lin Mojiao, has already stepped down.
لقد تنحى لين موجياو بالفعل عن منصبه.
Next, Lin Moqing,
التالي، لين موكينغ
President Lin,
الرئيس لين،
will take over as
سيتولى المنصب كـ
chairman of the company.
رئيس مجلس إدارة الشركة.
Due to the incident involving Chairman Lin,
بسبب الحادثة التي تورط فيها الرئيس لين،
many companies have already canceled their contracts with Lin Group.
ألغت العديد من الشركات بالفعل عقودها مع مجموعة لين.
The internal situation of the group
الوضع الداخلي للمجموعة
is also very precarious.
وهو أمر محفوف بالمخاطر للغاية أيضاً.
Although you are the son of the former chairman,
على الرغم من أنك ابن الرئيس السابق،
you are completely unaware of the internal affairs
أنت تجهل تماماً الشؤون الداخلية
about the internal affairs
بشأن الشؤون الداخلية
of the Group.
من المجموعة.
Why don't you
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
take over
الاستحواذ
the resort project
مشروع المنتجع
from Blue Crane
من بلو كرين
to stabilize
لتحقيق الاستقرار
the stock price
سعر السهم
and the cooperation
والتعاون
with other companies?
مع شركات أخرى؟
That's
هذا
how we can be convinced.
كيف يمكننا أن نقتنع؟
Am I right?
هل أنا على صواب؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
It makes sense.
هذا منطقي.
You have to convince us.
عليك أن تقنعنا.
Yes.
نعم.
I have 70% of the shares of Lin Group.
أملك 70% من أسهم مجموعة لين.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
How many?
كم عدد؟
5%.
5%.
2%.
2%.
Now.
الآن.
any other questions?
هل لديك أي أسئلة أخرى؟
How's it going?
كيف حالك؟
Did those old guys
هل فعل هؤلاء الرجال الكبار ذلك؟
force you to
يجبرك على
take on the resort project?
هل ستتولى مشروع المنتجع؟
Mengmeng wants Blue Crane to handle it alone.
يريد منغمينغ أن تتولى شركة بلو كرين الأمر بمفردها.
Lin Group won't intervene this time.
لن تتدخل مجموعة لين هذه المرة.
It seems that only in front of Miss Xu
يبدو أن ذلك يحدث فقط أمام الآنسة شو
our chairman
رئيس مجلس إدارتنا
is at a loss for words.
يعجز عن الكلام.
How's it going?
كيف حالك؟
What's the latest progress?
ما هو آخر التطورات؟
Are you free?
هل أنت متفرّغة؟
Country T happens to be short of a general manager.
تعاني الدولة "ت" من نقص في المدير العام.
Pack up and go there tonight.
جهزوا أنفسكم واذهبوا إلى هناك الليلة.
I'm busy.
أنا مشغول.
I'm doing business for hundreds of millions per second.
أنا أمارس أعمالاً تجارية بمئات الملايين في الثانية الواحدة.
I haven't finished yet.
لم أنتهِ بعد.
Then
ثم
I'll bring the project plan to you later.
سأحضر لك خطة المشروع لاحقاً.
Let's talk later.
لنتحدث لاحقاً.
Bye.
الوداع.
Come in.
ادخل.
Mr. Xu,
السيد شو،
here's the latest client information.
إليكم أحدث معلومات العملاء.
Please take a look.
يرجى إلقاء نظرة.
I passed by the front desk
مررت بجانب مكتب الاستقبال
and saw a package for you.
ورأيت طرداً لك.
So I
لذلك أنا
brought it up for you.
لقد طرحت هذا الموضوع من أجلك.
Thank you, Uncle Zhang.
شكراً لك يا عم تشانغ.
Just put it over there.
ضعها هناك فقط.
I heard
سمعت
that Mr. Lin has been...
أن السيد لين كان...
Uncle Zhang,
العم تشانغ،
I have to meet with the project team later.
يجب أن ألتقي بفريق المشروع لاحقاً.
Let's talk about other things
لنتحدث عن أشياء أخرى
later.
لاحقاً.
Okay.
تمام.
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
just go ahead and do it.
هيا، افعلها.
How are you doing lately?
كيف حالك هذه الأيام؟
Same old, same old.
نفس الشيء القديم، نفس الشيء القديم.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
what can I do for you?
ما الذي يمكنني أن أفعله من أجلك؟
This is...
هذا هو...
For you.
لك.
Do me a favor.
أرجو منك أن تسدي لي معروفاً.
Ms. Xu has a bad cervical spine.
تعاني السيدة شو من مشكلة في العمود الفقري العنقي.
Please give this to her.
أرجو أن تعطيها هذا.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
شكراً لك يا سيد لين.
I'll make sure to give it to Ms. Xu.
سأحرص على إعطائها للسيدة شو.
Ms. Xu,
السيدة شو،
here you are.
تفضل.
The fetus is developing well.
الجنين ينمو بشكل جيد.
All indicators are quite normal.
جميع المؤشرات طبيعية تماماً.
You need to maintain
عليك أن تحافظ
a happy mood.
مزاج سعيد.
It's not moving.
إنها لا تتحرك.
It's kicking.
إنها تركل.
Is it...
هل هو...
Is it kicking...
هل هي تركل...
me?
أنا؟
The baby is saying hello to you.
الطفل يحييك.
It's kicking again.
لقد عادت الأمور إلى سابق عهدها.
These little clothes
هذه الملابس الصغيرة
are so cute.
إنها لطيفة للغاية.
Yeah.
نعم.
I really hope that Xing can wake up
أتمنى حقاً أن يستيقظ شينغ
before the baby is born.
قبل ولادة الطفل.
Come in.
ادخل.
Mr. Xu,
السيد شو،
the resort project
مشروع المنتجع
has been completed.
تم الانتهاء منه.
The approval
الموافقة
has also been granted.
وقد تم منحها أيضاً.
We can start construction
يمكننا البدء في البناء
next week.
الأسبوع المقبل.
That's great.
هذا رائع.
Everyone has worked hard recently.
لقد عمل الجميع بجد مؤخراً.
After the groundbreaking ceremony,
بعد حفل وضع حجر الأساس،
let's organize a team-building event
لنقم بتنظيم فعالية لبناء الفريق
for everyone.
للجميع.
This is for the young people.
هذا مخصص للشباب.
I
أنا
won't join.
لن أنضم.
But
لكن
Yuanmeng Group
مجموعة يوانمينج
is also one of our partners.
وهو أيضاً أحد شركائنا.
How about
ماذا عن
inviting them to join us?
هل ندعوهم للانضمام إلينا؟
Okay.
تمام.
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
Mr. Xu, Mr. Zhang,
السيد شو، السيد تشانغ،
have something to eat first.
تناول شيئًا ما أولاً.
Dinner?
عشاء؟
I'm not eating.
أنا لا آكل.
I've already
لقد فعلت ذلك بالفعل
prepared dinner at home.
أعددت العشاء في المنزل.
I'll be heading out now.
سأغادر الآن.
Don't stay up too late.
لا تسهر لوقت متأخر.
Mr. Xu,
السيد شو،
you should go home and rest early.
يجب أن تعود إلى المنزل وتستريح مبكراً.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
شكراً لك يا سيد شو.
I'll be heading out now.
سأغادر الآن.